let hardadditionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 88 + 29",
        AnswerA: "115",
        AnswerB: "116",
        AnswerC: "117",
        AnswerD: "118",
        correctAnswer: "117",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 97",
        AnswerA: "110",
        AnswerB: "115",
        AnswerC: "120",
        AnswerD: "125",
        correctAnswer: "120",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 113 + 12",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "125",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 103",
        AnswerA: "138",
        AnswerB: "139",
        AnswerC: "140",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "141",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 106",
        AnswerA: "145",
        AnswerB: "146",
        AnswerC: "147",
        AnswerD: "148",
        correctAnswer: "147",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 115 + 22",
        AnswerA: "136",
        AnswerB: "137",
        AnswerC: "138",
        AnswerD: "139",
        correctAnswer: "137",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 111 + 17",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "128",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 118",
        AnswerA: "141",
        AnswerB: "142",
        AnswerC: "143",
        AnswerD: "144",
        correctAnswer: "144",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 + 119",
        AnswerA: "127",
        AnswerB: "128",
        AnswerC: "129",
        AnswerD: "130",
        correctAnswer: "128",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 117",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 + 27",
        AnswerA: "141",
        AnswerB: "142",
        AnswerC: "143",
        AnswerD: "144",
        correctAnswer: "144",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 115 + 15",
        AnswerA: "129",
        AnswerB: "130",
        AnswerC: "131",
        AnswerD: "132",
        correctAnswer: "130",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 116 + 17",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "133",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 118 + 23",
        AnswerA: "138",
        AnswerB: "139",
        AnswerC: "140",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "141",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 119 + 7",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "126",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 + 45",
        AnswerA: "122",
        AnswerB: "123",
        AnswerC: "124",
        AnswerD: "125",
        correctAnswer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 74 + 38",
        AnswerA: "110",
        AnswerB: "111",
        AnswerC: "112",
        AnswerD: "113",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 + 39",
        AnswerA: "121",
        AnswerB: "122",
        AnswerC: "123",
        AnswerD: "124",
        correctAnswer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 94 + 23",
        AnswerA: "116",
        AnswerB: "117",
        AnswerC: "118",
        AnswerD: "119",
        correctAnswer: "117",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 68 + 47",
        AnswerA: "114",
        AnswerB: "115",
        AnswerC: "116",
        AnswerD: "117",
        correctAnswer: "115",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 64 + 61",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "125",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 116",
        AnswerA: "138",
        AnswerB: "139",
        AnswerC: "140",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "139",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 + 25",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 + 9",
        AnswerA: "123",
        AnswerB: "124",
        AnswerC: "125",
        AnswerD: "126",
        correctAnswer: "126",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 + 41",
        AnswerA: "124",
        AnswerB: "125",
        AnswerC: "126",
        AnswerD: "127",
        correctAnswer: "124",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 87 + 36",
        AnswerA: "123",
        AnswerB: "124",
        AnswerC: "125",
        AnswerD: "126",
        correctAnswer: "123",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 112 + 34",
        AnswerA: "144",
        AnswerB: "145",
        AnswerC: "146",
        AnswerD: "147",
        correctAnswer: "146",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 106 + 28",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "134",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 + 50",
        AnswerA: "135",
        AnswerB: "140",
        AnswerC: "145",
        AnswerD: "150",
        correctAnswer: "150",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 + 47",
        AnswerA: "119",
        AnswerB: "120",
        AnswerC: "121",
        AnswerD: "122",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 + 39",
        AnswerA: "137",
        AnswerB: "138",
        AnswerC: "139",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "137",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 86 + 27",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "113",
    },
]